Guide to the postcard album 'Egypt and Palestine' from the Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref164
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Top: a postcard of the Tree of Virgin Mary in Al Matariyyah, Cairo. Bottom: a postcard of a painting of two men in regional dress, caption is verse Micah 7:14., Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000041; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
  Cairo, Egypt; Gardens; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing; Postcards; Paintings; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Canes/Walking Sticks; German Writing; Facial Hair
- Top: a postcard of a painting of men fishing in the Sea of Galilee, with sailboats in the background; caption is verse Matt 4:18 and John 11:3. Bottom: a postcard of a landscape of Tiberias and the coast of the Sea of Galilee., Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000042; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Paintings; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Men; Sea of Galilee/Lake Tiberias; Mountains/Hills; Lakes; Fish; Fishing; Coast; Buildings; Palm Trees; Head Covers/Veils
- A hand-colored postcard of the "Eighth Pylon of Heaven" in the Temple of Amun-Re, Karnak., 25 December 1913; AD_MC_030_ref164_000043; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
  Photographic Prints; Postcards; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Luxor, Egypt; Alexandria, Egypt; English Writing; Museums
- A painting of a group of people near the Sphinx and the Great Pyramids., Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000044; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
  Paintings; Postcards; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Pyramids; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Women; Umbrellas/Parasols; Camels; Animals; Regional/National Dress; Canes/Walking Sticks; Head Covers/Veils; Giza, Egypt
- A painting of the Colossi of Memnon with people in the foreground in Luxor, Egypt., Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000045; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
  Postcards; Paintings; Camels; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Fez/Tarboush; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Mountains/Hills; Luxor, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures
- A blank page in the Album "Egypt and Palestine.", Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000046; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
- A blank page in the Album "Egypt and Palestine.", Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000047; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
- The back cover of the Album "Egypt and Palestine.", Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000048; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
- A blank page in the Album "Egypt and Palestine.", Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000049; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)
- A blank page in the Album "Egypt and Palestine.", Circa 1910-1920; AD_MC_030_ref164_000050; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref164)